JORGE ALVAREZ



Personal details

Name
Jorge Alvarez

Address
Lima, Peru

Email winninglero@gmail.com

Wationality
Peruvian and french

LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com /in/jorgealvarezore/

□ Website
 https://jorgealvarezore.gi
 thub.io/

Skills

ArcGIS and AutoCAD

Power Bi

Web scraping

Numpy,
Pandas and
Tensorflow

Python and

Languages

Jupyter Notebook

Hobby

Play videogames

I am a passionate enthusiastic of Data Analyst and Data Scientist, always curious about the latest trends in the Data world. My degrees are: Technician degree in Surveyor at SENCICO, Bachelor's degree in Environmental Engineering at UNFV, Graduated in Master Degree in Mining and Environmental Management at UNMSM. My previous work experience was in Environmental Engineering specifically in GIS and CAD softwares.

Work experience

Geographic Information System Specialist (GIS)

Jan 2022 - Present

None (Freelancer)

Design and draw thematic maps for environment projects. Aptitudes: ArcGIS, ArcPy and Python.

Geographic Information System Specialist (GIS)

Feb 2018 - Dec 2021

JCI Ingeniería & Servicios Ambientales, Lima, Peru

Design and draw thematic maps for environment projects. Constantly update the internal geographic database. Aptitudes: ArcGIS, ArcPy and Python.

Computer Aided Design Specialist (CAD)

Oct 2012 - Apr 2013

2022

OHL, Challhuahuacho, Apurímac, Perú

Close to Graduated in Data scientist

Draw, design and doing some calculations in AutoCAD Civil 3D. Aptitudes: AutoCAD and AutoCAD Civil 3D.

Education

Platzi	
Graduated in Data analyst Platzi	2022
Graduated in Master Degree in Mining and Environmental Management UNMSM, Lima, Peru	2018 - 2019
Bachelor's degree in Environmental Engineerin UNFV, Lima, Peru	2007 - 2017
Technician degree in Surveyor SENCICO, Lima, Peru	2008 - 2010

Availability

Immediate

Various information

My Data scientist project:

https://github.com/JorgeAlvarezOre/Data_projects/blob/main/Phytogeographic_classification_model_v2.ipynb